Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Ivanoff, Andre M., Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 87)
- Ives, Jane K., Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 88)
- Iwanska, Alicja, Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 89)
- Iwanska, Alicja, Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 90)
- Izzard, Colin S., Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 91)
- Jaccard, James J., Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 92)
- Jaccard, James, Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 93)
- Jacklet, Alice, Undated (Box 19 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 94)
- Jacklet, Jon W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Jacklet, Jon W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Jacobi, Lotte, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Jacobs, Suzanne, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Jacobs, Ronald, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Jacobson, Dorothy T., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Jacobson, Dorothy, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Jacobson, Trudi, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Jaeger, Robert G., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Jagerson, Todd, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- James, Jasmine, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Jamison, Benton N., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Jamison, Benton, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Janecek, John, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Janesick, Valerie J., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Jelinek, Mariann, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Janower, David M., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Jarvenpa, Robert, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Jarvis, Dave, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Jean-Baptiste, Rachel, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Jefferson, Roslyn, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Jeffries, Leonard, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Jenkins, Joe W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Jenkins, Joe W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Jenks, David W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Jennings, Edward M., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Jennings, Edward M., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Jennings, John W., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Jerison, Michael, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Jerison, Michael, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Jerum, Kathryn J., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Jewett, Alice B., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Jiusto, James E., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Jiusto, James, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Johnson, Jacqueline, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Johnson, Judith, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Johnson, Kecia, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Johnson, Mauritz, 1955-1968 (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Johnson, Mauritz, Jr., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Johnson, Mary T., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Johnson, Pamela F., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Johnson, Robin Mackenzie, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Johnson, Sally, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Johnston, Peter H., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Johnstone, Bruce, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Johnstone, Bruce D., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Jones, Alethia, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Jones, Christopher C., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Jones, Gary L., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Jones, Gary L., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Jones, Jacquelyn, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Jones, Jeffrey J., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Jones, Jennifer, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Jones, Kenneth, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Jones, Shirley, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Jones, Shirley, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Jordan, Bojana Vuyisile, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Jorden, Frederick E., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Jordon, Lucious, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Jorgensen, June, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Joris, Pierre, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Joseph, Deborah, 2001 (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Josey, E.J., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Juedes, Donald R., 1994-1998 (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Jumpeter, Christine E., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Juncker, Paul, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Jurkowski, Janine M, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Jury, Mark, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Justeson, John, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Kaczor, Sue A., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Kadlecek, John, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Kadlecek, John A., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Kagan, Richard M., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Kahalas, Harvey, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Kakumba, Dawn V., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Kalish, Richard Jerome, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Kallman, Howard J., Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Kamberelis, George, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Kanes, Martin, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Kane, Shirley, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Kane, Shirley M., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Kaneko, Motohisa, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Kapechuk, Walter, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Garcia-Kapelewski, Martha, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Kanes, Martin, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Kapur, Deepak, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Karageorghia, Vassos, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Karlin, Kenneth D., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Karlson, Karleen, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Karpel, Leon, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Karpinski, Jakub, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Karsick, Margaret Barnes, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Karson, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Karuzan, O. Charles, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Kashiwase, Yasuji, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Kastle, Leonard, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Katagiri, Catharine M., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Katz, Daniel J., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Katz, Linda S., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Katz, Linda Steinberg, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Katz, Melvin L., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Katz, Melvin, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Katz, Selig H., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Katz, Sydney S., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Katz, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Katz, William A., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Kaufer, David S., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Kavanagh, Michael, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Kavanagh, Michael J., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Kazmierski, Georgiana M., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Kehe, Zhu, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Kekes, John, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Keller, Kevin E., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Keller, William E., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Kelley, Kathryn, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Kellner, Menachem, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Kellogg, Ruth, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Kelly, Brian V., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Kelly, Edward F., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Kelly, James F., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Kelly, Piret K, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Kelly, Richard, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Kelly, Richard, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Kelly, Thomas G., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Kelly, Thomas, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Kelsey, Jean, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Kemmerer, Frances, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Kemmerer, Frances, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Kemp, Barbara, 1994 (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Kendall, Kathleen A., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Kendall, Kathleen E., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Kendall, Richard, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Kendall, Richard H., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Kendra, Christopher - French Department Faculty 1964-1969, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Kenney, Ralph B., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Kenny, David George, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Keogan, Shonna, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Keohane, John J., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Keough, Brian, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Keough, Brian, 2001 (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Keough, Brian, 1999 (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Kern, Douglas, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Kersten, Christian, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Kessler, Jane, 2000 (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Kessler, Martin, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Ketterer, James, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Kettlewell, Karen, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Keyomarsi, Khandan, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Keys, Raymond, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Keyser, Daniel, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Khwaja, Haider, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Kidder, Amy Friedman, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Kielt, James P., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Kiepper, James J., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Kiepper, James J., 1964-1992 (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 84)
- Kifer, Allan, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 85)
- Kikuchi, Akio (visiting 1968-69), Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 86)
- Kilcullen, Thomas F., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 87)
- Kim, Jai S., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 88)
- Kim, Jai Soo, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 89)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 90)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 91)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 92)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 93)
- Kim, Yong Moo, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 94)
- Kimball, John, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 95)
- Kimball, Kenneth R., Jr., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 96)
- Kinal, Terrence W., Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 97)
- Kinard, Elissa, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 98)
- Kincaid, Lawrence, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 99)
- King, Carolyn, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 100)
- King, James, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 101)
- King, Jonathan, Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 102)
- King, Robert (chancellor), Undated (Box 21 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 103)
- King, Ryan D., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Kingma, Bruce, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Kinney, Thomas, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Kinney, Thomas, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Kirk, Russell, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Kirk, Stuart A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Kirwin, Arthur Jr., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Kivlen, Chris, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Kisseleff, Natalia, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Kizenko, Nadiezda, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Klages, Roy Arthur, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Klein, Alan F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Klein, Alan F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Klempner, Irving M., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Klempner, Irving M., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Kleppel, Gary, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Kleppel, Gary, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Klima, George, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Klima, George J., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Kline, David, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Klopott, R. Beth, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Klor De Alva, J. Jorge, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Knapp, Sara D., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Knapp, Sarah, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Knee, Michael J., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Knight, Christopher J., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Knight-Thomas, Dawn, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Knoblaugh, Cyril H., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Knoff, Howard M., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Knotts, Walter E., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Knotts, Walter E., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Knouse, Reno, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Knuth, Kevin, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Ko, Hai-Ping, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Koban, Charles, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Kobrin, David, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Koelmel, John (Jack), Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Koerner, Charlotte W., 1980 (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Koff, Robert H., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Kolb, Lawrence, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Kolesoff, Valerian F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Kolmin, Frank W., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Komisar, Jerome, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Kopf, Frank A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Kopka, Lynn M., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Kopka, Lynn M., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Koplow, Amy H., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Kopp, Steve, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Kopp, Rick, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Korenblum, Boris, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Korenblum, Boris, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Koseloff, Valerian F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Koslowski, Rey, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Kouba, Vicky, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Kowalchyk, John J., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Krahn, Mary L., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Kranich, Laurence Joel, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Krantz, Douglas K., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Kraus, William, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Kraus, William C., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Krause, Jo Ann, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Krege, George W., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Kress, Jack, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Kriger, Mark P., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Kressner, Herbert W., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Krohn, Marvin, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Krone, William, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Krosby, H. Peter, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Krosby, H. Peter, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Krull, Robert, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Kruzan, O. Charles, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Krykowski, Linda, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Krzykowski, Linda M., 1993 (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Kuemzli, Alfred, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Kuernan, Peter, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Kuethe, James L., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Kujawski, Ronald F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Kuivila, Henry G., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Kuivila, Henry G., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 84)
- Kulikowski, Robert R., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 85)
- Kumar-Tayi, Giri, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 86)
- Kupferberg, Audrey, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 87)
- Kupic, Mary, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 88)
- Kuritz, Hyman, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 89)
- Kurland, Norman, Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 90)
- Kusick, Colman F., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 91)
- Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 92)
- Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 93)
- Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 94)
- Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 95)
- Kuzn, I. Chen, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Kuznetsov, Igor, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- La Fond, Deborah, 1995 (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Labella, Vincent, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- LaCroix, Mina B., Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Lachmann, Richard, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Lachmann, Richard, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Lackman, Abraham, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Lagory, Mark, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Laferriere, Alaina, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- LaFlure, Spencer C., Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Lahiri, Kajal (also R. Hamilton Lankford), Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Lahiri, Kajal, Undated (Box 23 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)